Finding Aid for the Emily Driscoll and Thomas Brumbaugh Arts Autograph Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Emily Driscoll and Thomas Brumbaugh Arts Autograph Collection
1768-1935
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0121
.84 linear_feet
- Batty, Robert, February 15, 1845 (File 1)
- Bayliss, Sir Wyke, June 19, 1888 (File 2)
- Bird, Edward, April 12, 1814 (File 3)
- Blake, William, July 30, 1861 (File 4)
- Boyle, Eleanor V. C., February 20 (File 5)
- Bracebridge, Selina, No Date (File 6)
- Brockedon, William, April 9, 1828 (File 7)
- Burgess, John B., No Date (File 8)
- Bum-Jones, Georgiana, October 25, 1869 (File 9)
- Burton, Sir Frederic W., 1849-1893 (File 10)
- Callicott, Sir Augustus W., March 31, 1840 (File 11)
- Carpenter, W. H., 1858-1860 (File 12)
- Caw, James L., January 14, 1889 (File 13)
- Chalon, Alfred W., April 22, 1857 (File 14)
- Chantrey, Sir Francis, No Date (File 15)
- Cole, George Vicat, 1872-189 (File 16)
- Cole, Sir Etty Henry, January 12 March 19, 1849 (File 17)
- Collins, Charles, January 14, 1860 (File 18)
- Cook, Edward W., 1847-1877 (File 19)
- Cooke, George, No Date (File 20)
- Cotes, Francis, May 5, 1768 (File 21)
- Crofts, Ernest, March 17, 1889 (File 22)
- Doyle, John, No Date (File 23)
- East, Sir Alfred, 1899-1910 (File 24)
- Eastlake, Sir C. L., April 19, 1845 (File 25)
- Eastlake, Elizabeth, 1845-1867 (File 26)
- Etty, William, December 3, 1851 (File 27)
- Faed, Thomas, 1857-1894 (File 28)
- Farington, Joseph, June 11, 1810 (File 29)
- Fildes, Sir Luke, 1888-1893 (File 29a)
- Fitzgerald, Percy H., No Date (File 30)
- Forbes, Stanhope A., March 12, March 21 (File 31)
- Frith, Walter P., 1886-1888 (File 32)
- Furniss, Harry, January 14, 1895 (File 33)
- Gibson, John, December 29, 1855 (File 34)
- Gilbert, Sir John, 1885-1893 (File 35)
- Girtin, George W. H., 1885-1887 (File 36)
- Gow, Andrew C., No Date (File 37)
- Grant, Sir Francis, 1837, November 12 (File 38)
- Hayden, Sir Francis Seymour, 1871-1888 (File 39)
- Hall, Fred, May 15, 1893 (File 40)
- Hall, Sydney P., 1890 (File 41)
- Harding, James Duffield, No Date (File 42)
- Hayter, Sir George, November 9, 1860 (File 43)
- Henry, Napier, 1886 (File 44)
- Herbert, John R., 1867-1889 (File 45)
- Hoare, Prince, January 23, 1823 (File 46)
- Hunt, William Henry, February 23, August 20 (File 47)
- Hunt, W. Holman, February 19, 1865 (File 48)
- Kirkup, Seymore, August 21, 1871 (File 49)
- Landseer, Thomas, October 6, 1866 (File 50)
- Lawrence, Samuel, 1854-1881 (File 51)
- Lehmann, Rudolf, 1862-1872 (File 52)
- Leighton, No Date (File 53)
- Leitch, William L., September 4, 1869 (File 54)
- Leslie, Charles R., October 26, 1879 (File 55)
- Linton, William, August 14, 1830 (File 56)
- Lucas, David, January 10, 1855 (File 57)
- MacBeth, Robert W., 1889-1891 (File 58)
- MacWhirter, John, No Date (File 59)
- Magford, Henry, May 4, 1850 (File 60)
- Martin, Helena F., March 13 (File 61)
- Meadows, Joseph Kenny, 1857-1858 (File 62)
- Moore, Henry, 1886-1893 (File 63)
- Nicol, Erskine, 1857-1868 (File 64)
- North, John W., January 9, 1895 (File 65)
- Oakley, Octavius, 1830-1854 (File 66)
- O’Neil, Henry Nelson, August 14, [1860] (File 67)
- Ouless, Walter W., 1888-1889 (File 68)
- Partridge, Bernard, December 30, 1895 (File 69)
- Paul, R. B., No Date (File 70)
- Pennethome, Sir James, June 15, June 16, 1827 (File 71)
- Perugini, Kate, December 11, 1892 (File 72)
- Petrice, William Flinders, April 25, 1894 (File 73)
- Pickersgill, Henry W., [1830] (File 74)
- Prensep, Val, October 15, 1875 (File 75)
- Prout, John S., 1849-1852 (File 76)
- Prout, Samuel, No Date (File 77)
- Pye, John, 1846-1859 (File 78)
- Reed, E. T., August 9, August 13, 1909 (File 79)
- Richmond, George, 1853-1877 (File 80)
- Richmond, Sir William Blake, 1888-1893 (File 81)
- Riviere, Briton, 1886-1894 (File 82)
- Riviere, William, April 29, April 30 (File 83)
- Robinson, John H., 1846-1849 (File 84)
- Rooke, Thomas M., 1890-1902 (File 85)
- Ross, Sir William C., 1854-1855 (File 86)
- Rossetti, William M., January 25, 1912 (File 87)
- Rowbotham, Thomas C. L., June 30, 1863 (File 88)
- Samboume, Ed. Linley, May 15, 1892 (File 89)
- Scharf, Sir George, 1860-1869 (File 90)
- Sharpe, Eliza, May 1, 1847, Undated (File 91)
- Shepard, Dick, September 16 (File 92)
- Simpson, William J., 1861-1870 (File 93)
- Slade, Felix, December 20, 1859 (File 94)
- Smirke, Robert, November 7, 1806 (File 95)
- Smith, William, February 21, 1870 (File 96)
- Stanfield, Clarkson, 1825-1852 (File 97)
- Stanley, Dorothy Tennant, November 5, November 6, 1888 (File 98)
- Stephens, Fred George, 1861-1863 (File 99)
- Stevenson, Robert A. M., July 13, 1888 (File 100)
- Stone, Marcus, 1867-1897 (File 101)
- Tayler, Frederick, March 18, 1872 (File 102)
- Thomson, Henry, 1795-1819 (File 103)
- Vernon, Robert, 1833-1845 (File 104)
- Watts, Arthur, 1920 (File 105)
- Webster, Thomas, 1874-1883 (File 106)
- Weigall, Thomas H., November 26, 1856 (File 107)
- Weir, Harrison W., 1868, 1876, Undated (File 108)
- Wild, Charles, December 29, 1820 (File 109)
- Wiliams, Sam, April 20, 1805 (File 110)
- Wilton, Joseph, August 8, 1777 (File 111)
- Woodforde, Samuel, December 14, 1810 (File 112)
- Wynfield, David W., December 22, 1863 (File 113)
- Barker, Thomas J., Jr., June 13, [1856] (Box 2, File 1)
- Barry, Sir Charles, 1853-1854 (Box 2, File 2)
- Bell, John, June 29, 1848 (Box 2, File 3)
- Bouguereau, William, 1874-1891 (Box 2, File 4)
- Bowring, Sir John, January 11, 1834 (Box 2, File 5)
- Boxale, W., August 13, Undated (Box 2, File 6)
- Burne-Janes, Phil, October 28, 1921 (Box 2, File 7)
- Burton, Decimus, No Date (Box 2, File 8)
- Campbell, James Thomas, May 16, 1846 (Box 2, File 9)
- Campbell, T., No Date (Box 2, File 10)
- Catermole, L., 1845-1857 (Box 2, File 11)
- Collins, William, No Date (Box 2, File 12)
- Crawford, Francis Marion, May 25, 1892 (Box 2, File 13)
- Davis, Richard Harding, May 6, 1913 (Box 2, File 14)
- Doughty, Thomas, May 11, 1827 (Box 2, File 15)
- East, Sir Alfred, 1899-1910 (Box 2, File 16)
- Eastlake, Sir, C. L., April 19, 1845 (Box 2, File 17)
- Eaton, Walter Prichard, October 18, 1916 (Box 2, File 18)
- Fielding, February 4 (Box 2, File 19)
- Fildes, Luke, April 19, 1892 (Box 2, File 20)
- Foley, J. H., 1860-1864 (Box 2, File 21)
- Francia, Louis, No Date (Box 2, File 22)
- Frith, William Powell, 1868-1896 (Box 2, File 23)
- Furniss, Harry, No Date (Box 2, File 24)
- Glover, John, 1823 (Box 2, File 25)
- Heath, James, No Date (Box 2, File 26)
- Howard, Henry R. A., No Date (Box 2, File 27)
- Howard, J. M., May 1, 1826 (Box 2, File 28)
- Jackson, S. P., March 10, 1881 (Box 2, File 29)
- Lee, Sydney, September 2, [1835] (Box 2, File 30)
- Lequetre, Hippolyte Joseph, July 2, 1863 (Box 2, File 31)
- Loomput, Nicholas Van, No Date (Box 2, File 32)
- Marochetti, Charles, Baron, R. A., 1853 (Box 2, File 33)
- Martin, William, July 20, 1803 (Box 2, File 34)
- Moore, Henry, No Date (Box 2, File 35)
- Orpen, Sir William, No Date (Box 2, File 36)
- Pettie, John, 1874-1889 (Box 2, File 37)
- Pickersgile, J. W., July 25, 1848 (Box 2, File 38)
- Puvis de Chavannes, Pierre, November 29, 1897 (Box 2, File 39)
- Richmond, George, February 3, 1888 (Box 2, File 40)
- Rothenstein, William, February 24,1934 (Box 2, File 41)
- Ward, James, February 24,1934 (Box 2, File 42)
- Webb, Sir Aston, June 13, [1920] (Box 2, File 43)
- Williams, Joseph L., 1832 (Box 2, File 44)
- Woolner, Thomas, December 28, 1884 (Box 2, File 45)
- Unidentified Signatures, March 24, 1818, September 26, 1838 (Box 2, File 46)
- Letter about H. Quilter, Writer unidentified, February 1, 186? (Box 2, File 47)
- Letter from H. Quinter, February 18, 1886 (Box 2, File 48)
- Letters to H. Quilter, Writings Unidentified, 1886-1890 (Box 2, File 49)
- Brett, John to Quilter, March 11, 1890 (Box 2, File 50)
- Burdett, Henry to Quilter, May 10, 1894 (Box 2, File 51)
- Burnet, John, No Date (Box 2, File 52)
- Craftsmen, Art, No Date (Box 2, File 53)
- Creswick, Anne, May 3, 1866 (Box 2, File 54)
- Ford, John D. to Quilter, June 25, 1888 (Box 2, File 55)
- Greenwood, Colin H., August 4, 1875 (Box 2, File 56)
- Hayter, February 21, 1841 (Box 2, File 57)
- Hewitt, Florence A. to Dixon, No Date (Box 2, File 58)
- Issacs, Esther S. to Quilter, February 13, 1889 (Box 2, File 59)
- Joubert, F. to Dixon, April 9, 1861 (Box 2, File 60)
- Landseer, George to Dixon, No Date (Box 2, File 61)
- Lambert, L. Eng., January 16, 1890 (Box 2, File 62)
- Leighton, E. Blair to Quilter, 1889-1890 (Box 2, File 63)
- Kleen, Trya to Quilter, June 6, 1907 (Box 2, File 64)
- King, Ethel S. to Quilter, December 3, December 12, 1888 (Box 2, File 65)
- Leathart, James to Quilter, May 2, 1895 (Box 2, File 66)
- Lemon, Arthur to Quilter, March 17, March 18, and April 12 (Box 2, File 67)
- Leslie, G. D. to Quilter, 1888-1890 (Box 2, File 68)
- Montabla, Clara to Quilter, March 30, 1890, Undated (Box 2, File 69)
- Mozier, Joseph to Dixon, No Date (Box 2, File 70)
- Parsons, Alfred to Quilter, No Date (Box 2, File 71)
- Parton, Ernest to Quilter, March 21, 1889 (Box 2, File 72)
- [Pidder], John, August 14, 1875 (Box 2, File 73)
- Price, Luke, February 24, 1858 (Box 2, File 74)
- Rae, George to Quilter, February 12, 1894 (Box 2, File 75)
- Rathbone, Harold S. to Quilter, November 18, 1893 (Box 2, File 76)
- Reverdy, Edith, No Date (Box 2, File 77)
- Roberts, David, 1858-1861 (Box 2, File 78)
- Robinson, Henry, February 19, 1848 (Box 2, File 79)
- Roe, Fred, April 1892 (Box 2, File 80)
- Richmond, George, January 8, 1864 (Box 2, File 81)
- Sadler, Walter Dendy to Quilter, March 19, 1889 (Box 2, File 82)
- Sandys, Fred R. to Quilter, No Date (Box 2, File 83)
- Shield, J. to Quilter, June 1, 1886 (Box 2, File 84)
- Scott, William, May 31, 1890 (Box 2, File 85)
- Sketchley, R. F., March 11, 1865 (Box 2, File 86)
- Stephens, Fred G., November 18, 1884 (Box 2, File 87)
- Stokes, Adrian, 1880-1889 (Box 2, File 88)
- Story, G. A., 1889-1894 (Box 2, File 89)
- Temple, R., May 7, 1881 (Box 2, File 90)
- Thompson, Elizabeth Marie, 1865-1874 (Box 2, File 91)
- Tomson, Graham R., May 17, 1890, July 5, September 24 (Box 2, File 92)
- Ward, Edward M., 1867-1874 (Undated) (Box 2, File 93)
- Wiguelin, J. R. to Quilter, March 20, 1889 (Box 2, File 94)
- Williams, Alfred W., October 16, 1856 (Box 2, File 95)
- Wirgman, M. L., April 18 (Box 2, File 96)
- Woods, Hemy to Quilter, April 5, 1889 (Box 2, File 97)
- Wyllie, Charles W., March 19, 1889 (Box 2, File 98)
- Wyllie, W. L., March 18, 1890 (Box 2, File 99)
- Wyllie, W. M., August 11, 1863 (Box 2, File 100)
- [Wyongus], Rowan W., March 27, 1841 (Box 2, File 101)
- Reprinted Letters (Box 2, File 102)
- Batty, Robert, 15 February 1845; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Bayliss, Sir Wyke, 19 June 1888; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Bird, Edward, 12 April 1814; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Blake, William, 30 July 1861; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Boyle, Eleanor V. C., 20 February n.y.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Bracebridge, Selina, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Brockedon, William, 9 April 1828; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Burgess, John B., n.d.; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Burne-Jones, Georgiana, 25 October 1869; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Burton, Sir Frederic W., 1849-1893; ALS (6) (Box 1)
- Callcott, Sir Augustus W., 31 March 1840; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Carpenter, W. H., 1858-1860; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Caw, James L., 14 January 1889; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Chalon, Alfred W., 22 April 1857; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Chantrey, Sir Francis, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Cole, George Vicat, 1872-1893; ALS (5) (Box 1)
- Cole, Sir Etty Henry, 12 January, 19 March 1849; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Collins, Charles, 14 January 1860; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Cooke, Edward W., 1847-1877; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Cooke, George, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Cotes, Francis, 5 May 1768; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Crofts, Ernest, 17 March 1889; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Doyle, John, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 1)
- East, Sir Alfred, 1899-1910; ALS (5) & ANS (2) (Box 1)
- Eastlake, Sir C. L., 19 April 1845; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Eastlake, Elizabeth, 1845-1867; ALS (6) (Box 1)
- Etty, William, 3 December 1851, ANS n.d.; ALS (1) & ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Faed, Thomas, 1857-1894; ALS (3) & ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Farington, Joseph, 11 June 1810; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Flldes, Sir Luke, 1888-1893; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Fitzgerald, Percy H., n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Forbes, Stanhope A., 12 March n.y. & 21 March n.y.; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Frith, Walter P., 1886-1888; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Furniss, Harry, 14 January 1895; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Gibson, John, 29 December 1855; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Gilbert, Sir John, 1885-1893; ALS (5) (Box 1)
- Girtin, George W. H., 1885-1887; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- w, Andrew C., ALS (5) (Box 1)
- Grant, Sir Francis, 1837 & 12 November n.y.; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Hayden, Sir Francis Seymour, 1871-1888; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Hall, Fred, 15 May 1893; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Hall, Sydney P., 1890; ALS (5) (Box 1)
- Harding, James Duffield, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Hayter, Sir George, 9 November 1860; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Henry, Napier, 1886; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Herbert, John R., 1867-1889; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Hoare, Prince, 23 January 1823; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Hunt, William Henry, 23 February n.y. & 20 August n.y.; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Hunt, W. Holman, 19 February 1865; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Kirkup, Seymore, 21 August 1871; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Landseer, Thomas, 6 October 1866; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Lawrence, Samuel, 1854-1881; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Lehmann, Rudolf, 1868-1872; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Leighton, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Leitch, William L., 4 September 1869; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Leslie, Charles R., 26 October 1879; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Linton, William, 14 August 1830; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Lucas, David, 10 January 1855; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- MacBeth, Robert W., 1889-1891; ALS (6) (Box 1)
- MacWhirter, John, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Magford, Henry, 4 May 1850; ANS (1) (Box 1)
- Martin, Helena F., 13 March n.y.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Meadows, Joseph Kenny, 1857-1858; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Moore, Henry, 1886-1893; ALS (5) (Box 1)
- Nicol, Erskine, 1857-1868; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- North, John W., 9 January 1895; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Kley, Octavius, 1830-1854; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- O’Neil, Henry Nelson, 14 August [1860]; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Ouless, Walter W., 1888-1889; ALS (5) (Box 1)
- Partridge, Bernard, 30 December 1895; ANS (1) (Box 1)
- Paul, R. B., n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Pennethorne, Sir James, 15 & 16 June 1827; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Perugini, Kate, 11 December 1892; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Petrice, William Flinders, 25 April 1894; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Pickersgill, Henry W., [1830]; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Prensep, Val, 15 October 1875; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Prout, John S., 1849-1852; ALS (1) & ADS (1) (Box 1)
- Prout, Samuel, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Pye, John, 1846-1859; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- ed, E. T., 9 & 13 August 1909; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Richmond, George, 1853-1877; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Richmond, Sir William Blake, 1888-1893; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Riviere, Briton, 1886-1894; ALS (6) (Box 1)
- Riviere, William, 29 and 30 April n.y.; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Robinson, John H., 1846-1849; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Rooke, Thomas M., 1890-1902; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Ross, Sir William C., 1854-1855; ALS (4) (Box 1)
- Rossetti, William M., 25 January 1912; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Rowbotham, Thomas C. L., 30 June 1863; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Sambourne, Ed. Linley, 15 May 1892; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Scharf, Sir George, 1860-1869; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Sharpe, Eliza, 1 May 1847 and n.d.; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Shepard, Dick, 16 September n.y.; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Simpson, William J., 1861-1870; AM (2), ANS(1) (Box 1)
- Slade, Felix, 20 December 1859; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Smirke, Robert, 7 November 1806; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Smith, William, 21 February 1870; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Stanfield, Clarkson, 1825-1852; ALS (3), ANS (2) (Box 1)
- Stanley, Dorothy Tennant, 5 and 6 November 1888; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Stephens, Fred George, 1861-1863; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Stevenson, Robert A. M., 13 July 1888; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Stone, Marcus, 1867-1897; ALS (7) (Box 1)
- Tayler, Frederick, 18 March 1872; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Thomson, Henry, 1795-1819; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Vernon, Robert, 1833-1845; ALS (1), DS (Box 1)
- Watts, Arthur, 1920; ALS (12) (Box 1)
- Webster, Thomas, 1874-1883; ALS (2) (Box 1)
- Weigall, Thomas H., 26 November 1856; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Weir, Harrison W., 1868, 1876, n.d.; ALS (3) (Box 1)
- Wild, Charles, 29 December 1820; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Wlliams, Sam, 20 April 1805; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Wilton, Joseph, 8 August 1777; AD (1) (Box 1)
- Wood orde, Samuel, 14 December 1810; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Wyn ield, David W., 22 December 1863; ALS (1) (Box 1)
- Letter about H. Quilter writer unidentified, 1 February 186?; (1) (Box 2)
- Letter from H. Quilter, 18 February 1886; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Letters to H. Quilter writers unidentified, 1886-1890; (6) (Box 2)
- Brett, John to Quilter, 11 March 1890; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Burdett, Henry R. to Quilter, 10 May 1894; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Burnet, John, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Craftsman, Art, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Creswick, Anne, 3 May 1866; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Ford, John D. to Quilter, 25 June 1888; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Greenwood, Colin H., 4 August 1875; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Hayter, 21 February 1841; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Hewitt, Florence A. to Dixon, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Isaacs, Esther S. to Quilter, 13 February 1889; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Joubert, F. to Dixon, 9 April 1861; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Kleen, Tyra to Quilter, 6 June 1907; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- King, Ethel S. to Quilter, 3 and 12 December 1888; ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Landseer, George to Dixon, ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Lambert, L. Eng., 16 January 1890; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Leathart, James to Quilter, 2 May 1895; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Leighton, E. Blair to Quilter, 1889-1890; ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Lemon, Arthur to Quilter, 17 and 18 March n.y. & 12 April n.y; ALS (3) (Box 2)
- Leslie, G.D. to Quilter, 1888-1890; ALS (4) (Box 2)
- Montalba, Clara to Quilter, 30 March 1890, n.d.; ALS (1), ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Mozier, Joseph to Dixon, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Parsons, Alfred to Quilter, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Parton, Ernest to Quilter, 21 March 1889; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- [Pidder], John, 14 August 1875; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Price, Lucke, 24 February 1858; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Rae, George to Quilter, 12 February 1894; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Rathbone, Harold S. to Quilter, 18 November 1893; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Reverdy, Edith, n. d.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Roberts, David, 1858-1861; ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Robinson, Henry, 19 February 1848; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Roe, Fred, April 1892; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Richmond, George, 8 January 1864; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Sadler, Walter Dendy to Quilter, 19 March 1889; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Sandys, Fred R. to Quilter, ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Scott, William, 31 May 1890; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Shield, J. to Quilter, 1 June 1886; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Sketchley, R. F., 11 March 1865; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Stephens, Fred G., 18 November 1884; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Stokes, Adrian, 1880-1889; ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Story, G. A., 1889-1894; ALS (3) (Box 2)
- Temple, R., 7 May 1881; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Thompson, Elizabeth Marie, 1865-1874; ALS (2), ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Tomson, Graham R., 17 May 1890, 5 July & 24 Sept. n.y.; ALS (3) (Box 2)
- Ward, Edward M., 1867-1874 (Some have no dates); ALS (9) (Box 2)
- Wiguelin, J. R. to Quilter, 20 March 1889; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Williams, Alfred W., 16 October 1856; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Wirgman, M. L., 18 April n.y.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Woods, Henry to Quilter, 5 April 1889; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Wyllie, Charles W., 19 March 1889; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Wyllie, W. L., 18 March 1890; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Wyllie, W. M., 11 August 1863; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- [Wyongus], Rowan w., 27 March 1841; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Reprinted Letters, (5) (Box 2)
- Barker, Thomas J., Jr., 13 June (1856?); ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Barry, Sir Charles, 1853-1854; ALS (4) (Box 2)
- Bell, John, 29 June 1848; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Bouguereau, William, 1874-1891; ANS (2) (Box 2)
- Bowring, Sir John, 11 January 1834; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Boxale, W., 31 August n.y./n.d.; ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Burne-Jones, Phil, 28 October 1921; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Burton, Decimus, ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Campbell, James Thomas, 16 May 1846; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Campbell, T., n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Catermole, L., 1845-1857; ALS (3) & ANS (Box 2)
- Collins, William, n.d.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Crawford, Francis Marion, 25 May 1892; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Davis, Richard Harding, 6 May 1913; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Doughty, Thomas, 11 May 1827; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- East, Sir Alfred, 1899-1910; ALS (5) & ANS (2) (Box 2)
- Eastlake, Sir C.L., 19 April 1845; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Eaton, Walter Prichard, 18 October 1916; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Fielding, 4 February n.y.; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Fildes, Luke, 19 April 1892; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Foley, J.H., 1860-1864; ALS (2) (Box 2)
- Francia, Louis, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Frith, William Powell, 1868-1896; ALS (1) & ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Furniss, Harry, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Glover, John, 1823; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Heath, James, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Howard, Henry R.A., n.d.; (1) (Box 2)
- Howard, J.M., 1 May 1826; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Jackson, S.P., 10 March 1881; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Lee, Sydney, 2 September (1935?); ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Lequetre, Hippolyte Joseph, 2 July 1863; ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Loomput, Nicholas Van, n.d.; (1) (Box 2)
- Marochetti, Charles, Baron, 1853; ALS (3) (Box 2)
- Martin, William, 20 July 1803; (1) (Box 2)
- Moore, Henry, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Orpen, Sir William, n.d.; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Pettie, John, 1874-1889; ALS (6) (Box 2)
- Pickersgile, J.W., 25 July 1848; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Puvis de Chavannes, Pierre, 29 November 1897; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Richmond, George, 3 February 1888; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Rothstein, William, 24 February 1834; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Ward, James, 13 to 20 October 1643; (1) (Box 2)
- Webb, Sir Ashton, 13 June (1920?); ALS (1) (Box 2)
- Williams, Joseph L., 1832; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Woolner, Thomas, 28 December 1884; ANS (1) (Box 2)
- Unidentified Signatures, 24 March 1818; 26 September 1838; (2) (Box 2)